你不再微笑
You lost your smile
而且无处可寻
And it's nowhere to be found
你心中的烛光
The light you had
现在被埋葬在了土地中
is now buried in the ground
我找遍了整个城镇
I search for it all over town
然后我发现你打倒了自己
And I found you beating yourself down
亲爱的 我希望你了解到自身的价值
Oh babe, I wish you knew how beautiful you are
我希望你能通过我的眼睛欣赏自己
I wish you'd see yourself only through my eyes
然后你就知道这些应该马上就能过去了
Then you'll know in time this too shall pass
而你最后就能看清一切
And clarity will come to you at last
你迷路了
You lost your way
而周围没有指示
And there are no signs around
为了引导你回家
To guide you home
为了确保你安然无恙
To make you safe and sound
我要告诉你一件事
I may take one thing
这一件事
just one thing at a time
对自己好点
Be kind to yourself
这没什么坏处
it's surely in no crime
亲爱的 我希望你了解到自身的价值
Oh babe, I wish you knew how beautiful you are
我希望你能通过我的眼睛欣赏自己
I wish you'd see yourself only through my eyes
然后你就会开启新世界的大门
Then you'll know time will yield a new start
而你最后就能看清一切
And clarity will come to you at last
那天到来之前
Until the day comes
我都会坚定地支持你
I'll be right here by your side
我会努力让你明白
I'll try again and again to make you see
让你永远记住
You'll see you've got forever and a day
让你了却心愿
To be anything, everything you want to be
亲爱的 我希望你了解到自身的价值
Oh babe I wish you knew how beautiful you are
我希望你能通过我的眼睛欣赏自己
I wish you'd see yourself only through my eyes
时间将会治疗你悲痛的心
Then you'll know time will heal your aching heart
而你最后就能看清一切
And clarity will come to you at last
你最后就能看清一切
Clarity will come to you at last